<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Rohith's - QOD</title><link href="https://rohithreddy.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://rohithreddy.github.io/feeds/qod.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://rohithreddy.github.io/</id><updated>2020-07-03T00:14:00+05:30</updated><entry><title>Collection of Words / Sayings</title><link href="https://rohithreddy.github.io/2020/07/words-sayings.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-07-03T00:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-07-03T00:14:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Rohith Reddy</name></author><id>tag:rohithreddy.github.io,2020-07-03:/2020/07/words-sayings.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some Lines worth remembering&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Think fast and talk slow. Listen, analyze, evaluate, prepare a fallback strategy, then act. -Brain Collins&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Buy the best tools. You’ll only cry once. -Jim Cook&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The key is not the will to win… everybody has that. It is the will to prepare to win that is important” — Bobby Knight&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="QOD"></category><category term="QOD"></category></entry><entry><title>QOD 08 May</title><link href="https://rohithreddy.github.io/2020/05/mindset.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-05-08T00:14:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-05-08T00:14:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Rohith Reddy</name></author><id>tag:rohithreddy.github.io,2020-05-08:/2020/05/mindset.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Mindset&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Victims recite problems, leaders provide solutions --&amp;gt; Robin Sharma (probably)&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="QOD"></category><category term="QOD"></category></entry><entry><title>QOD 30 April</title><link href="https://rohithreddy.github.io/2020/04/life.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-04-30T00:07:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-30T00:07:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Rohith Reddy</name></author><id>tag:rohithreddy.github.io,2020-04-30:/2020/04/life.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Is life an illusion&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;"Life has no meaning the moment you lose the illusion of being eternal." - Jean Paul Sartre&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Reality is merely an illusion, albeit a very persistent one.” – Albert Einstein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Absurdity ---&amp;gt; Revolt, Freedom, and Passion&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="QOD"></category><category term="QOD"></category></entry><entry><title>QOD April 19 2020</title><link href="https://rohithreddy.github.io/2020/04/qod19042020.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-04-19T18:29:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-19T18:29:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Rohith Reddy</name></author><id>tag:rohithreddy.github.io,2020-04-19:/2020/04/qod19042020.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Another day another quote&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Whenever you find yourself on the side of the majority, it is time to pause and reflect — Mark Twain&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="QOD"></category><category term="QOD"></category></entry><entry><title>Quote for the Day April 14 2020</title><link href="https://rohithreddy.github.io/2020/04/another%20Day.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-04-14T23:38:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-14T23:38:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Rohith Reddy</name></author><id>tag:rohithreddy.github.io,2020-04-14:/2020/04/another Day.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Another day another quote&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;“I hated every minute of training, but I said, ‘Don’t quit. Suffer now and live the rest of your life as a champion.'” ~ Muhammad Ali&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I wish it need not have happened in my time," said Frodo. "So do I," said Gandalf, "and so do all who live to see such times. But that is not for them to decide. All we have to decide is what to do with the time that is given us.” - J.R.R. Tolkien&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"You don't have to be great to start, but you have to start to be great" Zig Ziglar&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="QOD"></category><category term="BrainFood"></category><category term="QOD"></category></entry><entry><title>Quote for the Day</title><link href="https://rohithreddy.github.io/2020/04/Food%20for%20the%20Brain.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-04-10T14:15:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-04-10T14:15:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Rohith Reddy</name></author><id>tag:rohithreddy.github.io,2020-04-10:/2020/04/Food for the Brain.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some Quotes that I have found inspirational or made me think&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;“The way a person does one thing is the way they do everything” -- Old Zen Saying&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Success is peace of mind, which is a direct result of self-satisfaction in knowing you did your best to become the best you are capable of becoming.” – John Wooden&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Success is liking yourself, liking what you do, and liking how you do it.” – Maya Angelou&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“To solve any problem, here are three questions to ask yourself: What could I do? What could I read? Who could I ask?” — Jim Rohn&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have to know what sparks that light in you so that you, in your own way, can illuminate the world.” — Oprah Winfrey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have to look deeply at every obstacle — it’s teaching you something or its asking you to pivot ---&amp;gt; Nikita Bharadia&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;source : &lt;a href="https://medium.com/live-your-life-on-purpose/if-you-have-failed-even-after-giving-your-100-then-you-need-to-do-this-5609013ab4e0"&gt;Nikita Bharadia's post on Medium&lt;/a&gt;  reminded me of somethings I needed to let go &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The intuitive mind is a sacred gift and the rational mind is a faithful servant. We have created a society that honors the servant and has forgotten the gift.” — Albert Einstein&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are three solutions to every problem: accept it, change it or leave it. If you can't accept it, change it. If you can't chnage it, leave it  --&amp;gt; Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The impediment to action advances action. What stands in the way becomes the way.” Marcus Aurelius&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Choose not to be harmed — and you won’t feel harmed.
Don’t feel harmed — and you haven’t been.” Marcus Aurelius&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Life is one big tug of war between mediocrity and trying to find your best self.” David Goggins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nothing can bring you peace but yourself.” Ralph Waldo Emerson.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What would you do if you weren’t afraid?” Spencer Johnson.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Let us prepare our minds as if we’d come to the very end of life. Let us postpone nothing.” Seneca.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;source : https://medium.com/swlh/how-to-thrive-after-being-laid-off-e755a21229b&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Never interrupt an enemy making a mistake” - Napoleon&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A long dispute means that both parties are wrong” - Voltaire&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We hardly find any persons of good sense save those who agree with us.” - François de La Rochefoucauld&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No man steps in the same river twice" - Heraclitus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We must all either wear out or rust out, every one of us. My choice is to wear out.” — Theodore Roosevelt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not what happens to you, but how you react to it that matters.” — Epictetus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The best revenge is not to be like that.” — Marcus Aurelius&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What happens to us is an objective reality,  how we respond is a subjective choice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The best revenge is not to be like that.” — Marcus Aurelius&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There is good in everything, if only we look for it.” — Laura Ingalls Wilder&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If you see fraud and do not say fraud, you are a fraud.” — Nicholas Nassim Taleb&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Every man I meet is my master in some point, and in that I learn of him.” — Ralph Waldo Emerson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Waste no more time arguing what a good man should be. Be one.” — Marcus Aurelius&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You are only entitled to the action, never to its fruits.” — Bhagavad Gita&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You are only entitled to the action, never to its fruits.” — Bhagavad Gita&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Self-sufficiency is the greatest of all wealth.” — Epicurus&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Tell me to what you pay attention and I will tell you who you are.” — Jose Ortega y Gasset&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Better to trip with the feet than with the tongue.” — Zeno &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Space I can recover. Time, never.” — Napoleon Bonaparte&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You never know who’s swimming naked until the tide goes out.” — Warren Buffett&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Search others for their virtues, thyself for thy vices.” — Benjamin Franklin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be tolerant with others and strict with yourself - Marcus Aurelius&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The world was not big enough for Alexander the Great, but a coffin was.” — Juvenal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“To improve is to change, so to be perfect is to have changed often.” — Winston Churchill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Time and patience are the strongest warriors.” — Leo Tolstoy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“No one saves us but ourselves / No one can and no one may.” — Buddha&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;source for above material https://medium.com/thrive-global/21-quotes-that-if-applied-change-boys-into-men-3e124aff36f8&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;read up on this really good article written by Benjamin Hardy &lt;a href="https://medium.com/thrive-global/how-to-take-ownership-and-change-your-brain-identity-and-future-252ffab07523"&gt; https://medium.com/thrive-global/how-to-take-ownership-and-change-your-brain-identity-and-future-252ffab07523&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Those who make the worst use of their time are the first to complain of its brevity.” ― Jean de La Bruyère, Les Caractères&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Selfishness is not living as one wishes to live, it is asking others to live as one wishes to live.” — Oscar Wilde&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A man who dares to waste one hour of time has not discovered the value of life.” ― Charles Darwin, The Life &amp;amp; Letters of Charles Darwin&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="QOD"></category><category term="BrainFood"></category><category term="QOD"></category></entry></feed>